{
	"games" : [
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "#1 The ancient Greeks worshipped many gods. Which of these gods did the Greeks worship?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Zeus",
		                "All of them",
		                "Athena",
		                "Poseidon"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 1
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "#2 What is the name of the Greek goddess of the earth?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Aphrodite",
		                "Demeter",
		                "Gaea",
		                "Hera"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "#3 If you cut off its head, two more grow back. Which animal does this describe?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Cerberus",
		                "Hydra",
		                "Gorgon",
		                "Chimera"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 1
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "#4 What is the name of the Greek god of the underworld?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Asclepius",
		                "Hermes",
		                "Hades",
		                "Pluto"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2 
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "#5 Every nine years, this monster required seven maids and seven youths to be fed to it.",
		            "content" : [
		                "The Nemean Lion",
		                "The Sirens",
		                "Cerberus",
		                "Minotaur"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        },
				{
				    "question": "#6 What is the name of the Greek god of war?",
				    "content": [
				        "Hercules",
				        "Hermes",
				        "Hades",
				        "Ares"
				    ],
				    "correct": 3
				},
				{
				    "question": "#7 What is the name of the Greek god of wine?",
				    "content": [
				        "Apollo",
				        "Zeus",
				        "Hermes",
				        "Dionysus"
				    ],
				    "correct": 3
				    
				},
				{
				    "question": "#8 Poseidon, god of the sea, had one animal in particular that was associated with him. What was it?",
				    "content": [
				        "Horse",
				        "Shark",
				        "Snake",
				        "Wolf"
				    ],
				    "correct": 0
				},
				{
				    "question": "#9 What is the name of the Greek goddess of love and beauty?",
				    "content": [
				        "Hestia",
				        "Aphrodite",
				        "Athena",
				        "Hera"
				    ],
				    "correct":1 
				},
				{
				    "question": "#10 What two gods were twin brother and sister?",
				    "content": [
				        "Demeter and Poseidon",
				        "Athena and Ares",
				        "Aphrodite and Hades",
				        "Apollo and Artemis"
				    ],
				    "correct": 4
				},
				{
				    "question": "#11 Who is the queen of the gods?",
				    "content": [
				        "Hera",
				        "Aphrodite",
				        "Demeter",
				        "Hestia"
				    ],
				    "correct": 0
				},
				{
				    "question": "#12 What powerful god lived in the Underworld rather than on Mount Olympus?",
				    "content": [
				        "Demeter",
				        "Hephaestus",
				        "Hades",
				        "Poseidon"
				    ],
				    "correct": 2
				},
				{
				    "question": "#13 What Greek hero was a son of Zeus and was required to perform many labors for the gods?",
				    "content": [
				        "Odysseus",
				        "Hercules",
				        "Achilles",
				        "Perseus"
				    ],
				    "correct": 1
				},
				{
				    "question": "#14 What was Apollo's most important daily task?",
				    "content": [
				        "Polishing the Moon",
				        "Cleaning the stables",
				        "Driving his Sun chariot across the sky",
				        "Washing the plates after dinner"
				    ],
				    "correct": 2
				},
				{
				    "question": "#15 Who were the Titans?",
				    "content": [
				        "The first Greek gods",
				        "The parents of the Zeus",
				        "Twelve gods that were overthrown by the Olympians",
				        "All of the above"
				    ],
				    "correct": 3
				}
		    ]
		}
	]
}